Previously on desperate housewives...
《绝望主妇》 前情提要
Port Scavo，you are under arrest.
波特·斯加沃  你被捕了
What?!
什么
Porter had nothing to do with that fire.
波特和那场火灾毫无关系
Apparently there is a witness that says otherwise.
可是有目击者指证了他
http://www.yyets.net/
人人影视版权所有  仅供学习交流
校对：小门柴  非燕
翻译：小门柴  非燕  Gloria  子非鱼  Chatte
总监：小树      压制：孤帆
时间轴： 小门柴  鱼儿
A witness? what are they talking about?
目击者  他们在说什么胡话
Porter was accused but not convicted.
波特被控告  却未被定罪
Katherine's love affair...
凯瑟琳的恋爱
I got the flowers.
我收到了你送的花
became serious.
动了真情
Mommy needs to lose a few pounds.
妈妈体重得减掉几磅
- You wanna help mommy be beautiful again?
-想帮妈妈重拾美貌吗
No.
不
As did gaby's resolve.
加布心意已决
Here's my cookbook.
这是我出版的烹饪书
And bree's success came at a price.
布里的成功  付出了昂贵的代价
You can be a little tough sometimes.
你可能有时太强势
- It's only to be expected.
-不用想也知道
I don't think I do that.
我觉得我不强势
I know you don't.
知道你没有自知之明
People don't talk about money in the suburbs...
人们在郊区  不谈论金钱
Mostly because they don't need to.
大多是因为他们无需言论
The ones who have it
有钱人家
Let you know with their brand-new clothes...
会让你看到他们添置新衣
Their expensive appliances...
购买昂贵电器
And their manicured lawns.
草地修剪整齐
The ones who don't have it
穷人家
Let you know with barbecues that need replacing...
让你知晓  他们陈旧的烧烤架
Walls that need painting...
掉漆的墙壁
And classic cars...
和香车
That need to be sold.
需要变卖
-Hey you go, walter. she's all yours.
-钥匙给你  沃尔特  车归你了
this is so awesome!
太好了
Where's tom? I wanna thank him
汤姆在哪里  我想向他道谢
- For making this the greatest day of my life.
-他成就了我人生最美好的一天
He's inside,
他在家里
But between sobs, he wished you happy driving.
可他抽泣时祝你一路顺风
Where is that man going with tom's car?
那人开着汤姆的车去哪里
Oh, that man is walter brotski, and he just bought it.
那人叫沃尔特·布罗斯基  刚买下那辆车
Tom loves that car. why would you sell it?
汤姆爱死那辆车了  为什么你会把它卖了
Sadly, we can no longer afford tom's midlife crisis.
很遗憾  我们负担不起汤姆的中年危机
Okay, here's the deal. we're...
好吧  是这样  我们
Sort of broke.
差不多破产了
Oh.Lynette.
勒奈特
Between porter's legal fees
我们要在波特的律师费
And that ghost town that we call a restaurant...
和那间镇上的废墟做出选择  尽管是个餐馆
-I thought scavo's was doing well.
-"斯加沃之家"生意很好
when times get tough,
经济不景气时
People do without things like pizza and sports cars.
人们不吃匹萨  不开跑车也行
- I am so sorry. I had no idea.
-我很遗憾  我不知情
It's okay.
没事
Just keep it under your hat. it's a little embarrassing.
别说出去  这事传出去我脸上挂不住
You should not be embarrassed.
别觉得不光彩
This is a horrible economy. we're all in the same boat. mm.
这是糟糕的经济惹的祸  我们处境相同
Hello, ladies. what do you think?
你们好  女士们  你们觉得怎么样
You bought a new car?
你买了辆新车
My book just made the "times'" best seller list.
我出的书刚上了《时代》杂志最佳畅销书榜单
They're talking 3-book deal, so I got the urge to splurge.
他们还要我续3本书  我等不及要挥霍一番
And look what just blew on my windshield at the stop sign!
瞧瞧我短停时  什么东西吹到风挡上了
Life is good.
生活真美好
Yes, people don't talk about money in the suburbs
没错  人们不在郊区谈论金钱
Because when they do,
因为几家欢喜
Other people get angry.
几家恼火
Whenever someone on wisteria lane
不紫藤巷里不管何时有人
Buys a new car,
买了新车
A simple ritual is performed.
都要进行一个简单的仪式
So how do you like my new car?
那你们觉得我的新车怎么样
- It's gorgeous!
- 太漂亮了
I am so jealous.
嫉妒死你了
I wish I had one.
我要有一辆就好了
But on this day,
可这天
One of the owner's friends
车主的一个朋友
Refused to participate in the ritual.
不愿多加赞扬
And even more surprisingly,
并且更令人吃惊的是
The owner of the car in question
正在夸夸奇谈的车主
Didn't seem to notice.
没有留心她的异常
Look, there's even a refrigerator.
还有个冰柜
The lexus dealer said there's just enough room
雷克萨斯的经销商说里面有足够空间
For a split of champagne and two chilled glasses.
放置一小瓶香槟酒和两个冰杯
And the best thing is, it's a hybrid
最棒的是  它使用混合动力
So you can barely hear it. let me show you.
基本听不到声音  给你们演示一下
Actually, I have to go to work.
其实我该回去工作了
But congratulations, bree. it's a beauty.
但恭喜你  布里  车很漂亮
Was it just me, or was that a little abrupt?
是我的原因  还是她走得太唐突
Eh, don't take it personally.
她不是针对你
I think she's got other things on her mind.
我想她被其它事搅乱了心神
Oh, dear. is something wrong?
亲爱的  出了什么事
Apparently, she and tom are having financial problems.
显然她和汤姆遇到了财政问题
They just had to sell tom's car.
他们刚变卖了汤姆的车
And you know, I saw her at the recycling center.
我看到她出现在废品回收中心
She was turning her cans in for money.
她当时正卖罐头换钱
That's, like, a half a step away
就好比把自己的卵子
From selling your eggs on the internet.
挂在网上变卖
And here I am, rubbing my fabulous new car in her face.
可我却在她面前炫耀我新买的香车
I feel awful.
我太差劲了
Oh, don't. how could you have known?
别自责  你怎么会知道她现在的遭遇
Thank god I didn't show her how the car parks itself.
谢天谢地我还没给她看  汽车如何自动停车
But you're gonna show us, right?
可你想演示给我们看  对吗
Well, it is pretty amazing!
真的很神奇
Well, it's nice to see you again, mrs. mayer.
很高兴再见到你  梅尔夫人
Thank you for agreeing to see us, mr. hobson.
谢谢抽空与我们会面  霍勃森先生
Running a school like oakridge
管理一所像奥克列吉这样的学校
Mustn't leave you with much...
让你不容你有太多
Free time.
空闲时间
Happy to oblige.
很高兴责成为您效劳
So I heard through the grapevine
我听传闻说
That there might be an opening for another student?
可能贵校还有一个入学名额
I assume you're referring to the henderson boy's expulsion
你想你是指亨德森家孩子被开除这事
Yeah. he bit his teacher, huh?
对  他打了老师  对吗
They had that problem
他们和哥哥托比
With their older boy, toby.
就经常打架
It's a family of biters.
真是个不安分的家庭
Well, the whole situation was incredibly unfortunate.
这整件事都相当不幸
But...We can't tolerate that kind of behavior.
可我们无法容忍这种恶行
Well, you wouldn't have to worry about that with m.j.
你无需担心m.j.会有此类问题
He's so well-behaved.
他品行端正
Look, I know how much you want your son at oakridge.
我知道你迫切希望儿子进入奥克列吉学校
You've called us every week for the past five months.
你过去5个月都每周都来电询问
I've been too pushy. oh, please don't take it out on m.j.
我知道我太心急  请别迁怒于m.j.
He is such a bright kid. say something in spanish.
他非常聪明伶俐  说两句西班牙语
I'm bored.
我烦透了
Be bored in spanish.
用西班牙语讲"烦透了"
Mrs. mayer, you can relax.
梅尔夫人  别紧张
We would love to have m.j. join us here.
我们很欢迎m.j.来本校就读
- Seriously?
-真的吗
Yes.
真的
As a matter of fact, his name was first on our waiting list.
其实他的名字在我们候选名单中排第一位
Fantastic!
太棒了
Here's a schedule for you.
给你课程表
Here are some insurance forms you need to fill out.
这些是你要填写的保险申请表格
And here's the tuition.
还有这是学费
As you can see, it's gone up a tad.
你也看到了  有点小涨
Yeah. that's quite a tad.
对  的确是"小涨"
But we're starting in the middle of the year,
可我们年中才上学
So we'd only pay half, right?
所以我们只需支付一半对吗
Yes. we've already prorated it. that is half.
对  我们已经按比例计算了  那就是一半
Fantastic.
太好了
Hey, I just thought of a way
我刚想到一个好节目
For us to celebrate our anniversary next week.
来庆祝我们结婚纪念日
What do you think about dinner at the palm?
在棕榈树餐厅共进晚餐怎样
The palm?
棕榈树餐厅
As in,
一进去
"they don't even show the prices on the menu" the palm?
"他们不在菜单上标示价格的"棕榈树餐厅吗
Honey, we're still paying off credit card debt.
亲爱的  我们还在偿还信用卡透支债务
Not anymore. the deal closed. I got the bonus.
已经还了  活干完了  我拿到了奖金
Oh, my god!
天呐
That's great!
太棒了
Oh, why didn't you tell me this
为什么今早
When you were begging for sex this morning?
求我和你同床时不说
You would've closed that deal, too. oh!
你同样能把活干完
Oh. we're rich again! hallelujah! well, we are not
我们又有钱了  哈雷路亚
"lighting cigars with $5 bills" rich,
我们没有"用5元债券点燃雪茄"那么富有
But we are headed in the right direction.
可我们奋斗目标正确
Oh! honey, we're gonna be us again--
亲爱的  我们又能回到从前了
The old carlos and gaby.
成为富有的卡洛斯和加布
You know what?
知道吗
I'm gonna wear my dress from the night you proposed.
我要穿上你向我求婚那晚穿的礼服
You still fit in that?
还穿得下吗
We're rich again! hallelujah!
我们又有钱啦  哈雷路亚
Have you not noticed me working my butt off?
你没有注意到我已经把肥臀减掉了吗
I'm almost back to the weight I was when we got married!
我已经减回了接近我们结婚时的体重
All I meant was...
我想说的是
You don't have to wear an old dress.
你不必穿旧裙子
I will buy you a new one.
我会给你买条新的
No, no. this'll be way more romantic.
不不  这样会更浪漫
I'm one good colonic away from being the old me!
我已经脱胎换骨啦
I'll call the restaurant.
我打电话去餐馆预约
They can write that on the cake.
他们可以在蛋糕上写上这话
Sorry. I know how much you loved that car.
抱歉  我知道你有多爱那辆车
This is all I have to remember her by.
这是我唯一缅怀她的方式
I called her "foxy." you wanna know why?
我叫她"狐狸精"  知道为什么吗
No.
不
Tom.
汤姆
I just heard. you sold the car?
我刚听说  你把车卖了吗
Yeah.
对
Well, we needed the money. the restaurant is dying.
我们需要钱  而餐馆也快倒闭了
Apparently, people don't wanna buy their pizza
显然人们不想从  纵火犯的父母
-From parents of an alleged arsonist.
-那里买匹萨
but porter didn't do it
但波特没有纵火
Well, maybe people still think that he's guilty,
可能人们还认为他有罪
Or maybe it's the economy.
或者可能是经济萧条原因
Or maybe it's both. I don't know.
也可能两者兼而有之  我不清楚
All I know is, I am driving a "dad car"
我知道的是  我在驾驶一辆"老爹车"
While some other guy is out rolling with foxy.
而其他人开着"狐狸精"招摇过市
Oh, buddy. I'm so sorry.
兄弟  我很遗憾
I wish there was something I could do.
希望能帮到点忙
We should get going.
我们得走了
But if we can help in any way, um, let us know.
有用得着的地方  吱个声儿
-Okay?
-好吗
thanks.
谢谢
Okay, what just happened back there?
好的  刚才怎么了
Nothing.
没什么
Oh, yeah. like that's gonna work.
越装越像
Why can't you ever remember who you're dealing with?
要装蒜  你可不是我的对手
Bob? bob? bob? bob-- I can keep this up all day.
鲍伯  鲍伯  鲍伯  鲍伯  不说我没完
-Bob?
-鲍伯
fine.
好了
The day the case against porter was dismissed,
波特的案子有些事我还没理清
I go over the discovery materials that the d.a. sent me.
于是我重新看了档案室发给我的材料
Okay? so?
是吗  怎么了
The witness who put porter in the storage room at the club,
说波特在俱乐部库房的目击证人
The only one linking him directly to the arson--
也是唯一可能嫁祸他纵火的人
Tom's helpful buddy there-- dave williams.
是汤姆的哥们  大卫·威廉姆斯
-What?
-什么
yeah.
没错
Porter wasn't even in the building.
波特根本不在那儿
What the hell is dave doing?
大卫到底干了什么
I don't know, but we have to tell tom and lynette.
不知道  但我们得告诉汤姆和勒奈特
No, that'll just get ugly.
不行  那样会得罪人
I'm okay with that.
我不在乎
Lee, the charges have been dropped.
李  这会给我们惹麻烦的
It's no longer our business.
不关我们的事
Besides, there's something about that dave guy
再说  还牵扯到大卫
That scares me.
我不敢
Oh, I don't get it!
我不懂
I'm only a few pounds away from my runway weight.
我只不过比标准体重多了一点点
-You want me to let it out?
-要改一下吗
that would be cheating.
那是自欺欺人
I'm gonna try to go pee again.
再去解个手
It's okay. you've had two children.
没关系的  你生过两个孩子
The weight redistributes. give in to it! I did.
身材变形很正常  想开点  看看我
Jean, you didn't just give in to it.
琼  你不是想得开
You slapped a piece of cheese on it.
你是往身上涂了层奶酪
Yeah, I said it. now just fix the hem.
我说话比较直  把边改一下
And this time, try not to leave the edges frayed.
这次  别留下毛边
Hey, edie! wait up!
伊迪  等等
Now don't forget, the clasp is broken.
别忘了  扣子掉了
Oh, I'll replace it.
我会缝上的
It may not match exactly.
但肯定会有瑕疵
But, um, your hair will cover it.
但  用你头发就能遮住
Jean, carlos is taking me to the palm, not out for hoagies.
琼  索利斯带我去棕榈树餐厅  不是吃快餐
Make it perfect.
做漂亮点
Huh. I see jean is back.
琼回来做你的裁缝师了
Ah, yeah. times are good.
风水轮流转
Not for her.
她没赶上
Her, mrs. mccluskey said something
麦克罗斯基夫人说
About you losing 5 pounds in one day.
你一天瘦了5磅
How'd you do that?
怎么做到的
I got drunk on bourbon and threw up all over her lawn.
喝威士忌酒还收拾了她整个草坪
No, not that story. something about a boot camp.
不是指这个  关于新兵训练营的
Oh, yeah. just started.
才开始没多久
Very military, very intense.
军事化  高强度的
That's perfect. I'm trying to fit in an old dress.
太棒了  我在试着穿上一条以前的裙子
I need intense.
我需要压力
forget it. you can't get in without a recommendation,
休想  没介绍人你进不去
-And I'm not recommending you.
-我不会引荐你的
why not?
为什么
Because you'd embarrass me. this is real exercise.
你为难过我  这就是原因
It's not the lotus position followed by a mocha latte.
那不是练瑜伽喝咖啡的地方
Oh, you're just afraid I'm gonna look better than you!
怕我身材好了把你比下去吧
6:00 a.m., the park. prepare to die.
早上6点  公园见  等着陪上小命吧
Jeez. this is the tuition?
天哪  这是学费
We're gonna blow his college fund on first grade.
我们想凑足他大学第一年的学费
I know, I know. we may have to give up a few luxuries.
我明白  我们不得不放弃些奢侈品
Yeah, like food and heat.
比如食物和高热量的
Okay, you know the problems they're having at his school.
你知道他们在那学校会遇到的问题
And now with all the budget cutbacks...
所以现在得缩减开支
I mean, this place is fabulous.
我是说  尽可能想得到的地方
Yeah, I'm not saying it's not. I'd kill to send him there.
我没说不是  但送他去那我承受不了
-But I just can't swing it.
-可我不能变卦
we've gotta do something.
我们得想想办法
My editor just quit,
我的编辑刚辞职
And my books are not exactly flying off the shelves.
我的书也才下架
Could you pick up some extra shifts? oh, yeah, I will...
还有其他办法吗  我会的
As soon as they create a 30-hour day.
要是一天有30个小时的话
I'm working around the clock.
我保证忙个不停
What about that big job you just did for the last 3 months?
你前3个月干的那份大差呢
What did you do with that money?
用那钱都干什么去了
Susan, we're not married anymore.
苏珊  我们已经离婚了
And what I do with my money is none of your business.
如何用钱  轮不到你来管
Yeah, well, if we were still married, you'd...
要是我们没离婚  你会
Probably would've waited until I finished my sentence.
听我把话说完的
What's this?
这是什么
A check.
支票
I understand you and tom are going through rough times.
我知道你和汤姆现在在困难时期
Thank you, but I can't accept this.
谢谢  但我不能接受
However, I would like to know how much I'm not accepting.
即便如此  我还是想知道我拒绝了多少钱
$20,000?!
两万美金
How many cookbooks are you selling, woman?
你的烹饪书卖了多少本  大姐
We just went to a second printing,
才开始印第二版
And now they're talking a 3-book deal.
现在在洽谈第三册的问题
So seriously, I am not gonna miss that money.
说真的  谁会跟钱过不去
That must be nice.
太好了
But... I can't accept it.
但  并不是白白接受
Why not? what's the point of success
为什么  成功的关键在于什么
If you can't share it with the people you love?
如果不能和爱的人分享
Because the people that you love may not pay you back,
因为爱的人无以为报
t-hen you stop loving them.
-就不再爱他们
then it's not a loan, it's a gift.
这不是负担  是礼物
Don't you have a birthday coming up?
你的生日不是快到了吗
And so do you.
你不也是么
And I'm gonna feel real crappy
我会觉得自己很逊色
When you unwrap your lavender bath beads.
当你打开紫色的沐浴香珠的时候
Come on, lynette.
勒奈特
You can't tell me this money won't take the pressure off.
有钱周转  总能帮上忙的
It would.
足够了
But I can't. I wouldn't want it to affect our friendship.
但我不能  不希望它影响我们的友谊
Okay.
好吧
Although...
要不...
How would you like to own
要是拥有
A piece of an italian restaurant? what?
意大利的餐馆怎么样  什么
It wouldn't be a loan or a gift.
它就既不是钱  也不是礼物
It would be... an investment
而是投资
That would buy you, say... 15% of scavo's.
你将有15%的股份
Oh! well, that's an intriguing offer.
是个够诱人的提议
If we do well, you get a cut of the profits.
要是经营得好  你还能分到部分利润
If we go belly-up, we liquidate, and you get the first 20000.
要是做垮了  都算我们的  你投资的两万还是你的
And then, of course, my family moves in with you.
那么  我全家都靠你了
So... do we have a deal?
那我们就成交喽
We most certainly do...
没问题
Partner.
合伙人
Some people think it's strange
可能有人觉得奇怪
I have a contract for my exercise class.
我的训练营要签协议
But I want people to understand
但希望你们明白
-The commitment I expect from them. I foun..
-我对你们的期望  以前...
here you go.
签好了
-All signed.
-都签了
you didn't even read it.
你都没读一下
Oh, no need. I'm up for anything.
没必要  我安排好了一切
Although I did just get a manicure,
虽然我留着指甲
So nothing that might chip a nail.
但丝毫不影响效果
Mrs. solis...
索利斯太太
Let me tell you what I learn in the israeli army.
让我告诉你  我在以色列军队所学到的
A group without commitment is a group that will fail.
没有承诺的组织早晚会解散
The women in my morning class are committed.
晨练班的妇女们都承诺过
I am starting to think
我开始怀疑
That you are not tough enough.
你够不够坚韧
Not tough enough?
不够坚韧
Let me tell you something, mr. iraqi army guy.
你给我听着  你这个伊拉克小兵哥
-Israeli.
-以色列
whatever.
那又怎样
I used to be a model, and you don't know what war is
我以前当模特的  你不懂什么是战争
Until you've been in a dressing room
直到走进更衣室
With a bunch of size zeroes reaching for the last rice cake.
和一群零尺寸的人面对最后一块米糕
-I am plenty tough.
-我才知道自己是那么有毅力
I'm not so sure.
简直不知所云
Hey, I know some of those women in your exercise class.
你训练营里有个人我认识
The most exercise they ever get is cutting a piece of cake.
每次训练完只能得到一小块蛋糕
That's a lap
那是禁忌
Excuse me? in the contract.
抱歉  协议书上
There are certain words I do not tolerate--
有些话是不许讲的
"cake," "tired,"
蛋糕  精疲力尽
"can't," "doughnut."
做不到  甜甜圈
If I hear them, you owe me a lap.
要是被我听到  你就要多跑一圈
It's an exercise class. why would anyone say "doughnut"?
这是个健身班  怎么会有人说油炸圈饼
That's another lap!
再加一圈
You know, maybe I should give this a little gander.
看来我该好好看看协议书
Come on, ladies!
加油  女士们
When I was in the special forces,
在特种部队时
We would do sit-ups in 115-degree weather.
我们要在115度的高温下做仰卧起坐
I still have sand in my ass.
我屁股里面进沙子了
You people are weak! let's go! let's go!
你们这些人真娇气  继续  继续
Gaby, knock it off.
加布  住口
You're gonna get us all in trouble.
你这样会给大家惹麻烦的
It's hard.
好辛苦啊
Of course it is. that's why it's called boot camp.
当然辛苦  所以才叫新兵训练营
Just hang in there, gaby. we all went through it.
坚持住  加布  我们都撑过来了
Shut up, mona. I'm puking air.
闭嘴  莫纳  我在呼吸
He's coming. get crunching.
他来了  快做动作
Hey! did I hear talking?
谁在说话
Sorry, sir! she got a little nauseous.
对不起  先生  她有点不舒服
I don't give a rat's ass what your problem is.
我不管你出了什么状况
You retch on your own time.
你在浪费你的时间
Okay. we need to talk.
我们谈谈
Gaby, no.
加布  不要
What the hell are you doing? get your butt back down!
你到底在干嘛  快躺下
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. time-out.
-暂停
time-out?
暂停
Look, I appreciate this whole military commando act,
我很欣赏这军事化的训练
But I'm new at this, and frankly, this is a bit much.
但我是新人  坦白的说  强度太大了
A bit much?
太大了
Yeah. are we gonna get a break soon?
休息一下不行吗
Oh. oh, we want a break.
我们要小憩
Like, maybe some coffee, some pastry?
比如  喝点咖啡  来点馅饼
Oh, that sounds so yummy.
听起来不错
You got any?
能提供吗
No, I don't got ! now get down or I'm gonna put you down
没有  要么自己躺下  要么我来扳倒你
I said time-out!
我说了"暂停"
There is no time-out! you signed a contract!
这儿没有暂停  你签了协议
Now get down!
现在给我躺下
Don't take that tone with me. I am paying. do it! do it!
不要用这种语气跟我说话  我付了钱
Aah! do it! do it! do it!
躺下  躺下
Who brought her here?
谁带她来的
That would be me!
是本人
Sorry, sir!
对不起  长官
Because of edie,
因为伊迪
Our 2-mile run is now 4 miles!
两英里长跑变四英里
Oh, my god. look at those. wow!
天呐  快看
hey. what's going on?
怎么了
Oh, susan, you gotta check these out.
苏珊  你该看看这个
Oh, please don't make a fuss.
别大惊小怪的
They're magnificent. susan, look at 'em.
太漂亮了  苏珊  快看
- Uh, what am I looking at exactly?
-我要看什么
The pearls.
珍珠项链啊
Oh, those. oh, they're stunning.
项链  太漂亮了
Oh. thank you.
谢谢
Well, I have a big bar mitzvah to prep. see ya.
好了  我还要准备一场大型成人礼  再见
Oh. mm. she's so lucky.
她真走运
Mike is such a great guy.
麦克是个好男人
What? mike bought those? he bought her pearls?
什么  是麦克买的  给她买了珍珠
He's a keeper.
他盯得很紧
Oh, that's right. you didn't keep him, did you?
对了  你没看住他  是吧
Hi. lynette, hi I wish I had time for a chat,
勒奈特  我想跟你谈谈
But I'm on my way to a meeting.
可是我要去开个会
I might design my own line of bakeware. can you imagine?
我可能会设计自己的烘焙用具  你能想象吗
-This will just take a sec.
- 就一小会儿
okay.
没问题
Tom and I are so grateful for your investment
我和汤姆非常感谢你的投资
That we want to do something special for you.
我们想为你做些特别的事情
oh, that sounds lovely.
听起来很不错
We'd like to shut scavo's down for the night
我们打算把今晚把斯加沃之家关了
And throw a party in your honor. just family and friends.
为你开个派对  只邀请家人和朋友
We'd toast your success and have a night of fun,
庆祝你的成功  大家过个愉快的晚上
Just like old times. what do you say?
就像以前一样  你觉得怎么样
oh, that sounds nice.
真不错
Can we walk and talk?
边走边说吧
-Yeah, yeah.
- 好的
you know what might be even better?
你知道怎么办得更好吗
My publisher has been begging me
我的出版商求我
To do a local launch for my book. hmm.
给我的书在当地办个发布会
I could do a signing at your restaurant
我可以在你的餐馆里签名售书
And finally fill the place.
最终肯定会爆满
Would you hold that for a moment? oh.
帮我拿一下好吗
Well, we've filled the place many times, but it's your party.
我们爆满过很多次  这是你的派对
Whatever you want.
你想怎么样都行
oh, you can just put that on a hanger in the back.
把它挂在后面就行了
What I want is to make this an opportunity for you.
我要做的就是给你个机会
We can turn one of your dismal thursday night seatings
我们可以在生意不好的周四晚上办
Into a real event.
办的有模有样
I don't know what to say.
我不知道说什么好
Well, don't thank me. it was your idea.
不用谢我  是你的点子
Right.
对啊
Glad I thought of it.
很高兴这是我的点子
Susan mayer knew she couldn't always give her son
苏珊·梅尔知道她不能把所有的东西
Everything she would've liked...
都给她的儿子
But when she saw her child's tuition
可当她看到孩子的学费
Around katherine mayfair's neck,
戴在凯瑟琳的脖子上
She felt something had been stolen from him.
她觉得应该从麦克那偷点东西
And it didn't take her long to decide...
而且很快做了决定
How she was going to get it back.
她将如何把它抢回来呢
Susan, hi. hi. you at home?
苏珊  你在家吗
Uh, yeah. I'm just about to jump in the shower. what's up?
在  正打算洗澡呢  怎么了
I'm going crazy 'cause I think I left my front door unlocked.
我要疯了  我好像忘了锁门
Could you run and check? I'll stay on the line.
你能帮我过去看看吗  我等着你
No, no. I totally understand.
没事  我可以理解
The one day I don't lock up,
要是有一天我忘了锁门
I always think that's the day somebody's gonna break in.
总觉得那天会有小偷进去
Exactly.
就是
And so even though I was already halfway to the airport,
我刚才在去机场的半路上
I turned around and I came home,
可是现在又掉头回来了
And, yep, I had left the garbage disposal on.
是啊  我曾把垃圾箱盖开着
So ever since then, I always check.
从那以后  我总要检查一下
Oh, I'm the same way. anyway, you can relax.
我也是这样  不管怎样  你放心吧
- The front door's all locked up.
-前门是锁着的
Oh, you know what?
你知道吗
I'm actually still worried about the side door.
再帮我看看侧门吧
Do you think you could check that, too?
能帮我看一下吗
already did. you're good.
看过了 锁着的
Well, I'm gonna take that shower now. see ya later, hon.
好了  我要洗澡了  回头见  亲爱的
Mike, is that you?
麦克  是你吗
You're just in time.
回来的正是时候
Susan?
苏珊
Susan mayer!
苏珊·梅尔
For god sake, give me back my pearls!
看在上帝的份上  项链还我
Pearls or towel-- you decide.
项链还是浴巾  你来选
You wouldn't dare.
你敢
I have been naked on this street.
我以前在这里裸体过
It would be nice to take the heat off that story.
是该来点新鲜故事了
have you lost your mind?
你疯了吗
Mike said he can't afford to pay for m.j.'s private school.
麦克说他付不起M.J上私立学校的学费
Now I know why.
现在知道原因了
He wants to see his girlfriend wearing pearls
他想让他的女朋友戴着珍珠项链
When she flashes him.
光彩照人
What? he wouldn't pay for m.j.'s school?
什么  他付不起M.J的学费
No. so I was going to take these
不是  所以我来拿这个
And sell them to try to pay for it,
把它卖了  然后交学费
And, yes, now that I'm saying it out loud,
是啊  我现在要公布于众
I hear how stupid that sounds.
听起来真是愚蠢
I can't believe mike would do that.
麦克怎么会这么做
Well, he did.
他就是做了
Hey, mrs. mayfair.
梅菲尔夫人
It's nice to see you.
见到你真高兴
Perhaps we should discuss this later.
我们该待会再谈
This can't be good.
大事不妙啊
So is this a "welcome home, we missed you" kind of thing
这是在欢迎我回家吗
Damn right, "oh." what happened to "i'm broke"
别大惊小怪  "我破产了"是怎么回事
And can't afford to send m.j.to private school"?
还说没钱送M.J上私立学校
don't get me wrong, mike.
麦克  别误会
It was a wonderfully generous present.
这礼物棒极了
But you can't go around blowing your kid's money
可是你不能用供孩子的钱
On jewelry for your girlfriend.
给女朋友买珠宝
What did these cost you? $4,000, $5,000?
花了你多少  四千还是五千美元
$129.
129美元
What?
什么
They're fake, okay?
这是假的  行了吧
And I knew how badly you wanted pearls,
我知道你很想要珍珠项链
And I couldn't afford real ones.
我买不起真的
And the salesman swore you'd never know the difference,
推销员发誓你一定分不出真假
And she didn't.
她的确没分出来
At least you won't feel bad if you ever lose them.
至少丢了也不会觉得难过
I just wanted to get you a really nice gift,
我只是想送你件不错的礼物
And I don't know.
不知道怎么说
I-i guess I was embarrassed when I couldn't.
我想如果不送你的话  会觉得很不好意思
Mike, don't ever feel
麦克  别这么想
Like you have to spend money to impress me.
别觉得花钱才能打动我
Okay?
好吗
Trust me.
相信我
I'm already very impressed.
我已经很感动了
Ugh. okay, okay. point made.
好吧  好吧  水落石出了
Move along
各回各家吧
I'll go fix us some dinner
我去做晚饭
How dare you
你怎么这样
I didn't know they were fake
我不知道那是假的
I mean how dare you think
我是指你怎么竟敢认为
That I would put jewelry for my girlfriend
我会拿着该给儿子上学的钱
Ahead of my son's education
去哄女友开心
Okay   maybe I jumped to conclusions
可能是我妄下结论
But this school is important for m.j.
但这个学校对m.j.真的很重要
I feel really bad that we're falling short
我们快资金不足了  我觉得很沮丧
Susan, I've been at work since 6:00 this morning
苏珊  我今早6点就开始工作
And after I inhale a 5-minute dinner
晚饭才吃了5分钟
I'm going back out till midnight
又要一直工作到午夜
I am busting my ass to give our son the best
为了给儿子创造条件  我呕心呖血
So if we're falling short. it's not because of me
我们如果真的缺钱  也没我什么责任
What?
什么事
Where are you? you're late for training
你在哪  你训练迟到了
Oh, yeah, I quit that
是的 我退出了
There is no quitting. it's in the contract
条约讲明了  不许退出
Yeah, well,  maybe you should take it up with my lawyer
那好吧  让我律师跟你说
Here he is
让他听
We are not leaving!
我们决不闪人
Come on, ladies! keep going!
加油  女士们  继续
Keep it moving!
不要停
What the hell do you think you're doing?
你们在这里干什么
When you don't come to boot camp
你不来训练营
Boot camp comes to you, fall in!
那训练营就找上门  快下来
-Are you out of mind? I have two sleeping children.
-你疯了吗  我两个孩子都在睡觉
I know
我知道
I've seen the cellulite
我已经看到了肥臀
-Fall in!
-下来
do it, gaby, there is no quitting
快来吧  加布  不许退缩的
Oh, don't get all holier than thou mona
别假惺惺的
I saw you pull into the doughnut shack yesterday   doughnut--that's a lap!
我亲眼见你昨天吃了甜甜圈
doughnut--that's a lap!
甜甜圈  那是禁忌
Oh, really? well, try this on for size
真的吗  那我不妨这么说
I'm going back to bed because I'm tired
我太"累"了  我要回去睡觉
And when I wake up, maybe I'll have some cake
起床后  我还要吃些"蛋糕"
And you can't stop me
而你"管不了"我
Gaby!
加布
Where are you going?
你去哪
If you don't get out there
你要是不回去
He is gonna take it out on the rest of us
他就要拿我们当出气筒了
Well, frankly, some of them need it
老实说  有些人是需要好好锻炼
I just came for a little remodel
我只是要重塑一下身型
And there are some real teardowns out there
但那简直就不是人干的
you are one spoiled selfish little brat
你简直就是个淘气自私的小混蛋
Oh, for god sakes, edie, it's a stupid exercise class
看在上帝的份上  伊迪  这是个愚蠢的训练班
I tried it, it sucked, I don't want to do it anymore
我参加了  烂得很  不想再去了
-Lighten up
-你醒醒吧
well, that stupid little exercise class is filled
这愚蠢的训练班上的女性们
With women who bust their asses three times a week
每周三次坚持痛苦的训练
While raising kids and holding down full-time jobs
还要带孩子  做全职家务
Well, they're crazy. he yells and they jump
说明她们疯了  他一边叫  她们就一边跳
He tells them to run all the way over here, and they do it
他叫他们怎么跑就怎么跑
He didn't make us come here.  we agreed to
不是他强迫我们来的  是我们说好要来的
What the hell for?
什么意思
Because you told us
因为是你告诉我们
That it was important to you to get into that dress
穿上那件礼服  对你意义非凡
So we came here to support you
所以我们特地前来给你打气
You wanted the old gaby back?
你想要以前的加布回来吗
congratulations, you got her--
恭喜你  你成功了
A self-centered, obnoxious jerk
一个自以为是的讨厌鬼
Personally, I liked poor,  paunchy gaby better
老实讲  我还是喜欢又穷又肥的加布
At least she had some humility
至少她有点人情味
Okay, time to stretch
伸展训练开始
Not you!
不是你
You are 25 minutes late,  give me 50
你迟到了25分钟  做50个
Oh, my god, you're her!
天呐  你就是书上的人吗
Well, technically, I'm she, but yes
是的  我正是此人
Your turkey tetrazzini saved my marriage
你的脆皮烤火鸡挽救了我的婚姻
Would you sign this for me?
帮我签个名行吗
Certainly
没问题
I am so excited to be tasting your food tonight
真高兴今天能尝到你的美食
My food? what are you talking about?
我的美食  你说什么呢
Oh, it says here the chefs of scavo's
斯加沃之家的主厨
- Are going to be making recipes from your book.
-将为您呈现烹饪书的佳肴
They are?
真的吗
I can't wait to try that four cheese pizza
我等不及要尝尝那块4层芝士披萨
you might have to
希望你能尝到
Excuse me
失陪
Lynette
勒奈特
I understand you and your fellow chefs
我听说你和你的厨师们
Will be serving my four cheese pizza tonight
今晚将提供4层芝士披萨
Yep, just adding the parmesan
是啊  现在要洒帕尔马干酪
But that's commercial parmesan
但那是市面上卖的帕尔马干酪
So?
那又怎样
So that's like the dust they sweep off the floor
那就好比用扫把在玷污
Of a place that makes real cheese
生产正宗芝士的地方
Oh, no, it's fine. we use it all the time
没关系  我们一直用这种
Oh,  perhaps you do.  but my recipe specifies fresh grated
或许你这么干  但我的食谱指明用新鲜碎芝士
Bree, no one will notice
布里  没人吃得出来
Parmesan is the fourth cheese in a four cheese pizza
帕尔马干酪是最上面的一层
It's the ringo of these cheeses
是4层芝士的最外层
Mr.scavo said the grease trap is overflowing again
斯加沃先生说隔油池又溢出来了
Oh, for pete sake. I'll be right back
真是麻烦  我很快回来
take your time
慢慢处理
I'm sorry, we haven't been introduced
不好意思  我还没有自我介绍
I'm bree hodge,  part owner
我是布里·霍吉  合伙人
Hi, I'm cindy, we'll chat later
你好  我是辛迪  一会儿再聊
Roll out some dough and show me where the basil is
在揉点面团  告诉我罗勒油在哪
We'll be serving three cheese pizza tonight
我们今晚做3层芝士披萨
But what about the pizzas that we just made?
那刚才做的那些怎么办
Tom, I can't tell you how happy I am for you
汤姆  我真为你感到高兴
-This place is packed, it's packed!
-这里满座了  爆满了
yep
是啊
You know what? bree really came through for us
告诉你  布里帮了我们不少忙
Wait wait, even if she hadn't
等等  即使她没帮忙
You would have landed on your feet
你们也完全能自力更生
I had total faith in you
相信你们的才干
and you have had three scotch and sodas
你喝了三杯威士忌苏打
Dude, this money goes right in your pocket
兄弟  钱进了你们口袋
Mm! I'm just supporting you
这是给你们捧场
I gotta go check on that grease trap
我要去看看隔油池
I gotta get back to edie.  she wanted me home by 10:00
我回去陪伊迪了  她让我10点前回家
But, dude, congratulations.
哥们儿  祝贺你
I'm proud of you.
真为你骄傲
- See ya.
-回见
You bet.
好的
Hey, Tom?
汤姆
Yeah?
怎么了
Nothing. never mind. you're busy. you know, wait.
没事儿  算了  你那么忙  等等
I just want you to know that...
我只是觉得你应该知道
-That guy's not your friend.
-那个家伙可不是你的朋友
who? dave?
谁  大卫
Is there someplace we can talk?
换个地方再说
Yeah.
好
Son of a...
混蛋...
If this doesn't stop your mother-in-law
如果这样还是不能阻止你婆婆
From criticizing your cooking, I will give you a full refund.
挑剔你的厨艺  我会给你全额退款
Hey, can I borrow you a sec?
你能来一下吗
-Now, they are waiting.
-现在吗  他们在等着呢
you'll be a celebrity in 5 minutes.
5分钟后你就继续神采奕奕
Come on.
快点
Excuse me.
失赔
You want to explain this?
怎么解释
Oh, dear. I was hoping to spare your feelings,
亲爱的  我也希望能不伤害你的感情
But since you know, I wasn't comfortable having my recipe
只是我不太喜欢用不合格的食材
Made with substandard ingredients.
按我的配方烹饪
We use that parmesan all the time.
我们一直都用这种帕尔马干酪
You can't go changing things without asking me.
你不应该没问过我  就擅自做决定
Hey, you made me partner.
是你让我当合伙人的
I can change 15%, and I chose the parmesan.
我有15%的决定权  我决定帕尔马干酪
And I don't know if you've heard,
我不知道你听到没有
But people are raving about my pizza.
大家极力夸赞我的披萨
Well, they probably would have loved my pizza, too,
他们也很有可能会喜欢我的披萨的
But we'll never know,
不过已经没有可能性了
Because my partner threw it in the garbage. what a waste.
因为我的合伙人把我的披萨扔进了垃圾桶  多可惜
Fine. I'll reimburse you, if that'll make things right.
好吧  如果你愿意的话  我会补偿你的
Oh, sure. it's only money, right?
是的  只不过是钱而已
What's that supposed to mean?
你这么说是什么意思
We all know how well you're doing, Bree.
布里  我们都知道你多么成功
You have made that very clear.
你已经充分证明了你自己
But you shouldn't be lording it over everybody
但你也不能就这样对每个人都指手画脚
I've worked my ass off to get where I am.
我勤勤恳恳工作才成就了今天的我
I've worked my ass off, too. I just wasn't as lucky as you.
我也勤勤恳恳辛辛苦苦  我只是没有你运气好罢了
Well, I've always believed that we create our own luck.
我一直都认为机会是自己创造的
Meaning that I've created my own failure?
你是说我的失败是我自己造成的
Well, not completely, but let's face it. you do cut corners.
不完全是  但必须承认  你确实偷工减料了
I mean, one of the things I can teach you
我能教给你的
-Is importance of the attention to detail.
-就是一定要注意细节
talk about luck.
说到运气
When I offered to throw you this little thank-you party,
当我提出为你举办个感恩聚会的时候
I never imagined that it would turn into an opportunity
我可没想到这会变成
for me to learn from the great Bree Hodge.
一个向伟大的布里·霍吉学习的好机会
Well, I'm not the one who needed $20,000
我不是那个需要两万块
to keep my business afloat.
来维持生意的人
No, you're the one who's never gonna let me forget it.
当然不是  你是那个想让我永远铭记大恩的人
Where are you going?
你去哪儿
Home. tell me how the party I threw for you turns out.
回家  回头告诉我这个聚会怎么样
Lynette, I- I- I don't understand why you're so upset.
勒奈特  我不明白你为什么这么生气
I know you don't,
我知道你不懂
But five years ago, you would've.
不过要是在5年前  你会懂的
My car!
我的车
You know that was an accident, right?
你知道是个意外
I did the best I could on the clasp, Mrs. Solis.
索利斯夫人  对那个扣子我已经尽全力了
I don't think you'll be able to tell the difference.
我觉得您应该看不出区别来
Okay, be honest.
好吧  说老实话
Here I come.
我出来啦
So what do you think?
觉得怎么样
You are stunning.
真是太迷人了
Radiant.
太美了
Really?
真的吗
Really.
真的
You're back, Mrs. Solis,
索利斯夫人  风采依旧
Exactly like you were before.
和以前真是一模一样
Oh, I think I've changed a little bit.
我觉得还是有些变化
Not that I can see.
我是没看出来
If there's nothing else, I'll be going.
没什么事儿  我这就走了
Jean, wait.
珍  等等
What is it? Is there a problem?
怎么了  哪儿不对吗
No, no. it's perfect.
不是的  礼服很完美
I just want to tell you
我只是想告诉你
how helpful you've been to me over the years,
这些年你真的帮了我许多许多
and I'm really grateful.
我真的很感激你
Thank you.
谢谢你
Hey, buddy. How was the rest of the...
哥们儿  后来...
I know what you did.
我知道你做了什么
-What?
-什么
don't give me that!
别来这套
I know that you told the cops that Porter set that fire.
我知道是你告诉警察说波特放的火
I didn't say he set the fire.
我没说是他放的火
I only said I saw him in the back hallway.
我只是说我在后台看到了他
You couldn't have! he wasn't there!
你没看见  他根本不在那儿
Tom, the cops were really grilling me.
汤姆  是那些警察盘问我
They wouldn't let up.
他们不肯放手
I had to tell them what I thought I saw.
我只好告诉他们我看到的
Porter could have gone to jail.
波特可能会坐牢的
You almost destroyed my family, destroyed our business.
你几乎毁了我的家庭  我的事业
I'll make it up to you. I swear.
我会做出补偿的  我发誓
I never meant to hurt you or lynette.
我从没想过伤害你或是勒奈特
Oh, lynette doesn't know about this. I didn't tell her.
勒奈特还不知道这件事儿  我没告诉她
If I had, you'd be dead.
如果我告诉她了  那你死定了
I am so sorry.
真的很抱歉
I never should have said anything to the cops.
我不应该和警察说那些话
It was dark. I'd been drinking. you've gotta believe me.
当时光线很暗  我喝了酒  你得相信我
Stop.
别闹了
Just stop.
Are you done?
你闹够了吗
This is crazy.
太疯狂了
I mean, there's gotta be some way we can work this out.
我们肯定能解决这件事儿的
We're friends.
我们是朋友
That's what I thought, too.
我曾经也那么以为
But I don't know who you are.
但现在不是了
Tom.
汤姆
Can I ask you something?
我能问你点事儿吗
Go ahead. shoot.
说吧
I've been thinking a lot
最近我想了许多事儿
about your first wife.
关于你的前妻
Edie.
伊迪
I know. Just one question, and then I'll shut it.
我知道  就问一个问题  就不问了
I don't like talking about her.
我不喜欢说她的事儿
It has been weeks since I found out she even existed,
我知道她的存在有几个礼拜了
And I've never mentioned her once.
可我一次都没提过
Come on. Look at this as my reward.
把这个问题当作是奖励好了
Okay.
好
One question.
就一个
Being married to her...
你和她的婚姻
or being married to me... mm.
和我们的婚姻比较的话
What's the biggest difference?
最大的不同之处是什么
Honestly?
说实话
Our marriage is more real.
我们的婚姻更加真实
Really?
是吗
In what way?
哪方面呢
Well, with her, it was like...
和她的婚姻  就像是
a fairy tale.
一个童话
I thought it would last forever.
我曾经以为我和她会永远在一起
It didn't.
结果没有
What you and I have is more real
而我们之间就更真实了
Because I know it's not forever.
因为我知道我们不可能永远在一起
When I hold you,
我每一次拥抱
when I kiss you,
每一个吻
I try to remind myself to appreciate the moment,
我都一直提醒自己要珍惜
Because tomorrow may never come.
因为也许我们没有将来
Love...
真爱
Is just temporary.
是短暂的
The way the fairy tale ends...
童话的结局
Is death.
是死亡
My first instinct
我的本意
Was to ask you if she was prettier than me.
是想问你  她和我谁更漂亮
When will I learn to go with my gut?
我什么时候才能学会随心所欲呢
I'm sorry. you can't afford the tuition?
你说什么  你无法承担学费
No.
是的
But I read in your brochure
不过你们的宣传册上写着
That faculty members get a 50% discount,
教职工子女能减免一半的学费
So for your art department,
你们的美术部门
How would you like to hire
愿不愿意聘用
An award-winning children's book illustrator
我这位获过奖的儿童漫画家
Who is great with kids and has a face you can't say no to?
我很喜欢孩子  而且我的美貌让人很难拒绝吧
Unfortunately,
不好意思
Our art department is fully staffed.
我们的美术部门人手足够了
Can't say no.
不能说"不"
Miss mayer,
梅尔小姐
I appreciate your enthusiasm
我很欣赏你的热忱
And the face,
还有你的美貌
But I'm afraid it just won't work out.
但恐怕真的不行
I wish you the best of luck.
祝你好运
Yes.
是的
Right.
好吧
No, wrong.
不  太糟糕了
Miss mayer, please, I'm so busy.
梅尔小姐  我公务繁忙
Look, I know I said that m.j. was a star student,
我说过m.j.是个尖子生
But the truth is,
事实上
He's one of those kids that needs extra attention.
他格外需要老师的关心
The classes at his school are way too big,
他们学校的班上  学生太多
And I see higetting lost in the shuffle.
我发现他在混乱中变得很迷惑
And if he gets lost now...
如果他就这样掉队了
My ex-husband is doing everything that he can,
我的前夫为了m.j.尽了全力
And I need to know that I am, too.
我想我也可以
I will serve lunches.
我可以去食堂打工
I will be a janitor.
我也能去看门房间
Anything.
什么工作都行
But I am not walking out on my son's future.
我会为我儿子的未来竭尽所能
Well, one of our art teachers does need an assistant,
我们有个美术老师需要一名助手
But you're completely overqualified.
不过这样可能大材小用了
I'll take it.
我愿意做
Congratulations on your new job.
恭喜你有了份新工作
Congratulations
恭喜您
On getting me out of your office.
终于把我赶出您的办公室了
What's that?
是什么来着
A check for the damage to your car.
修车的赔偿
I can't afford to go through my insurance company.
让保险公司经手我赔不起
It's just the bumper.
只是碰到保险杠而已
You don't need to do that.
没必要这么做的
Yes, I do.
有必要
And the minute we're back on our feet,
只要我们有条件
I am gonna pay back your investment--
会第一时间归还你的投资款
Every penny,
连本带利
With interest.
一分不差
Lynette, stop. wait. please. don't be this way.
勒奈特  等等  拜托  别这样
I don't want money to get in the way of our friendship.
我不想让钱破坏我们的友情
Yeah...
是吗
I think it's a little late for that.
我觉得已经来不及了
There's a lot you can do with money in the suburbs.
在郊区  有钱好办事
You can payfor a night on th
可以在镇上渡过美妙的一夜
You can provide a private school education.
可以送孩子去私立学校念书
You can purchase a token of affection.
可以购买礼物表达爱意
But the one thing you must never do with money
但是敬告  千万不要把金钱
Is use it as a weapon,
当作武器
Because someone...
因为有人欢喜
Always gets hurt.
就有人恼火